(Sheldon:)turning her into
the Grand Empress:
(Sheldon:)a piece combining the power
(Sheldon:)of the knight, queen
and serpent.
(Leonard:)Elegant.
(Sheldon:)That's because it's simple.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, I look forward
to playing with you.
(Scene:)And...
(Leonard:)And what?
(Sheldon:)And a third person.
(Sheldon:)It's three-person chess.
(Amy:)I must say,
ever since you started
(Sheldon:)having regular intercourse, your
mind has lost its keen edge.
(Sheldon:)You should reflect on that.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, but Einstein had
a pretty busy sex life.
(Sheldon:)Yes, and he never unified
gravity with the other forces.
(Sheldon:)If he hadn't been
such a hound dog,
(Sheldon:)we'd all have time machines.
(Leonard:)Got it. Bye.
(Sheldon:)You know I'm right.
(Leonard(outside apartment):)I think he's getting worse.
(Amy:)Oh, my metatarsal are barking.